<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="general_questions_intro">These are some of the general questions that a student may want to know before coming to Miami Dade College, select a topic to learn more!</string>
    <string name="main_message">Hello, and welcome to the School of Engineering and Technology, also known as Entec, at Miami Dade College North Campus!</string>
    <string name="stem_message">"These are the Bachelor Programs that the School of Engineering and Technology offers." +
                "From Artificial Intelligence, Networking, to Electrical Engineering, and many others, Miami Dade College offers a variety of STEM programs for students interesting in developing skills for a career in technology." +
                "Select a program for more information."</string>
    <string name="advisement_info_message">
    At Miami Dade College, advisors are here to help you navigate your academic journey.
    They provide assistance with course planning, career guidance, transfer options, and personal development.
    You can visit the Advisement and Career Services department in person or online for personalized support.
    </string>
    <string name="learning_options_message">Miami Dade College offers flexible learning options to fit your needs. "
                + "You can choose in-person classes, blended formats combining online and traditional instruction, "
                + "MDC Live for real-time virtual learning, or fully online courses for flexibility. "
                + "Explore these options to find the learning style that works best for you.
    </string>
    <string name="scholarships_message">Miami Dade College offers a variety of scholarships "
                + "to support students in technology programs. These include the Javier Coto Scholarship, City of Miami Residents Scholarship, "
                + "and the FPL Tech Scholarship. Explore these options to help fund your academic journey in engineering and technology. "
                + "For more details, contact the EnTec department or visit the scholarships webpage.
    </string>
    <string name="financial_aid_message">Miami Dade College is dedicated to making higher education affordable and accessible for everyone. "
                + "Through a variety of financial aid options, including grants, scholarships, loans, and work-study programs, "
                + "students can pursue their education without financial barriers. "
                + "MDC is committed to supporting your journey with resources and guidance to help you achieve your academic goals. "
                + "Read the screen to learn more about the financial aid opportunities available at Miami Dade College.
    </string>
</resources>
